In the last lecture we made sure that we can also remove ingredients from the burger, now I want to update
Son dersimizde, burgerdeki maddeleri kaldrabileceimizden ve burger fiyatn ne
the burger price and display it as part of that burger too.
zaman gncelleyeceimizi ve burgerin bir paras olarak grntleyebileceimizden emin olduk.
Now actually, if I add a lot of ingredients to a burger, it is scrollable because we configured it to
imdi Aslnda burger iin pek ok malzemeyim olsayd kaydrlabilir olurduk nk onu
be,
yaplandrdk.
so the price should probably display it above the build controls, let's say.
Diyelim ki fiyat muhtemelen inaat denetimlerinin zerinde gsterilmelidir.
So in the build controls here, besides outputting the controls,
Dolaysyla toplu kontroller burada kontrolleri ktlyor.
I want to show the burger price and we can simply use a paragraph here where we say current price colon
Burger fiyatn gstermek istiyorum ve burada u anki fiyat iki nokta stste diyebileceimiz bir paragraf kullanabilirsiniz.
and then I expect to get the price passed in with props.
Ve sonra fiyatn sandklarla geirilmesini bekliyorum.
So props.price, something like that.
Yani pervane fiyat byle.
Now the price is calculated in the burger builder container,
imdi fiyat Bergere Boulder konteyneri iinde hesaplanr.
here we have the total price state. So I want to pass this price to my build controls then because that is where
Burada toplam fiyat durumumuz var, bu fiyat kabark kontrol S10'a gemek iin S10'a tkladk, nk
I just added the usage of that property.
bu sadece o mlkn kullanmn ekledi.
So let's add the price property,
Bylece fiyat mlkn ekleyelim.
the name I just picked in build controls and pass this.state.totalPrice,
Oluturduum ad kontrol ediyor ve bu devlet toplam fiyatn geiyor.
make sure to save all files and let's have a look,
Tm Follett'leri kaydettiinizden emin olun ve bir gz atalm.
we see the current price here
Mevcut fiyat burada gryoruz.
and if I add ingredients, you see this price increases, here however we get it back with decimal numbers
Ve eer malzemeleri eklersem, fiyatn arttn grrsn, ancak javascript'te ondalk sayya geri
in javascript so we should fix this and maybe we also want to print that in
dnersek, bunu dzeltmeliyiz ve belki de hepsini de bastrmak istiyoruz.
well, emphasized.
yi vurguland.
So what we can do in the build controls for one, let's wrap this in a strong tag,
Dolaysyla, kada sarl olann yapm denetimlerindeki yapabileceklerimiz gl etikettedir.
the price so that is basically with font-weight
Bylece fiyat esasen yaz tipi arl ile.
bold and let's fix it by fixing this price here.
Cesur ve bu fiyat burada sabitleyerek dzeltelim.
Now for that, price needs to be a number but thankfully it is,
imdi bu fiyat bir numara olmal ama neyse ki yle.
so now we can call toFixed on it and fix it to two decimal places.
imdi bunu dzeltip iki ondalk basamakta dzeltmek iin arayabiliriz.
Let's save this
unu kurtaralm.
and now we see four
Ve imdi drt gryoruz.
and if I start adding, you see the price goes up. I guess we built a quite affordable burger here which
Ve eer size eklemeye balarsam fiyatn arttn grrm sanrm insanlar burada olduka lezzetli grnen olduka
looks really delicious.
uygun fiyatl bir burgere giderler.
So with that, the burger builder is actually in pretty good shape.
Bylelikle burger kurucusu aslnda olduka iyi durumda.
The check out button is missing but that's something I will add in a second
Kontrol dmesi eksik, ancak saniyede ekleyeceim bir ey var.
and thereafter we need to take care about all that navigation which is hidden here at the top.
Ve bundan sonra en stte bulunan tm gezinme hareketlerine dikkat etmeliyiz.